<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<start>
<patientarrives>
    When you arrive at the ED on your own and not in an ambulance, you will first go through a triage process.
  <registeredpatient>
      Region
      	Registered patients per fully qualified GP FTE
       South West	2023
     East of England	2478
      North West	2244
      South East	2367
   <availablenurse>
    nurseAiman
    <recordhealthcondition>
       After the nurse records the patient's health condition, the patient waits for an available doctor. The patient then receives an assignment to the next available
    <availabledoctor>
     <waitforavailabledoctar>
       doctarArsalan.
      </waitforavailabledoctar>
    <assignpatienttodoctor>
      <needfollowup>
        they are booked back-to-back-to-back with patient appointments, and if they spend extra time with one patient, it just makes them late for the next one, and it snowballs from there.
      <arrangeappointment>
          Some can cure an illness by killing or halting the spread of invading germs, such as bacteria and viruses
         <needmedication>
           <givepatientprescription>
                 The superscription includes the date the prescription order is written; the name, address, weight, and age of the patient; and the Rx (Take)
            </givepatientprescription>
           </needmedication>
           <patientleaves>
              Poor experiences with providers who rush and lack listening skills are a top reason patients leave. 
            </patientleaves>
        </arrangeappointment>
       </needfollowup>
     </assignpatienttodoctor>
    </availabledoctor>
      <assignpatienttodoctor>
         Physician-patient panels
    Identify a patient's main physician provider by looking at the number of visits they've had with a generalist or medical subspecialist over a period of time. 
    Demographic and visit characteristics
   Consider factors such as age, gender, and whether the patient is new or seeking help for an acute problem. For example, patients who are younger than 65, male, or new patients are more likely to be assigned to a physician assistant (PA). 
         </assignpatienttodoctor>
     </recordhealthcondition>
     <waitforavailablenurse>
     DrAsim
      </waitforavailablenurse>
    </availablenurse>
  <registerpatient>
     RS:1000
  </registerpatient>
   </registeredpatient>
</patientarrives>
</start>